gigaparts.com 2019-08-29

# Privacy and Cookie Policy GigaParts.com

**What we collect**

**Information you voluntarily provide to us:** When you sign up for and use our website, consult with our customer service team, send us an email or communicate with us in any way, you are voluntarily giving us information that we collect. That information may include your name, physical address, email address, IP address, phone number, as well as details including gender, occupation, location, purchase history, and other demographic information. By giving us this information, you consent to this information being collected, used, stored by us and disclosed to trusted third parties that we partner with as needed.

**What we do with the information we gather**

We use this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and it may be used or disclosed in the following ways:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. You can stop receiving our promotional emails by following the unsubscribe link included in every email.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
  * To enforce compliance with our Terms of Use and applicable law.
  * To meet legal requirements, including complying with court orders, valid discovery requests, valid subpoenas, and other appropriate legal mechanisms.
  * To provide information to representatives and advisors, including attorneys and accountants, to help us comply with legal, accounting, or security requirements.
  * To prosecute and defend a court, arbitration, or similar legal proceeding.
  * To respond to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
  * To trusted third parties we engage with, but only to the extent necessary to perform the service they provide.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be due. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this request using our [Contact Us](https://www.gigaparts.com/contact/) page.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Third Party Vendors and Cookies  **

Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on other web sites and cookies are used to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website and partner websites. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

If you wish to save this privacy policy for future reference, please print this page.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at  256-535-4442 or via email at [privacy@gigaparts.com](mailto:privacy@gigaparts.com?Subject=Privacy%20Concern)**
